<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Node id="205401" name="AsyncCommand" thumb="box">	
	<NodeMap>
		<Project 
			name="AsyncCommand Utility for AS3" 
			status="Production"
			repo="Utility_AS3_AsyncCommand" 
			tag="AsyncCommand_1_0"
			version="1.0"
			archive="AS3/Utility_AS3_AsyncCommand.zip" 
			docs="AS3/Utility_AS3_AsyncCommand/asdoc-standard/"
			live=""
			forum="topic=831.0"
			owner="Duncan Hall"
			owner_node="312"
			pic="PureMVC-Framework-AS3-Std-MC.png"
			shot="">
			
<Description><![CDATA[
The AsyncCommand utility offers a solution to the problem of executing a series of commands each of which may need to complete one or more asynchronous operations before the next command is executed. 
]]></Description>						

<ReleaseNotes><![CDATA[
<B>Features in Version 1.0</B>
<UL><LI>IAsyncCommand interface defines the methods required for an asynchronous command, which at the moment is only setOnComplete, which sets a callback method for the IAsyncCommand implementer to call when it has completed its task.</LI>
<LI>AsyncCommand class extends the framework SimpleCommand class and implements IAsyncCommand.</LI>
<LI>AsyncMacroCommand class extends Notifier and implements IAsyncCommand. Accepts IAsyncCommands or ICommands for subcommands. This means any combination of SimpleCommand, MacroCommand, AsyncCommand or AsyncMacroCommand.</LI>
<LI>Standard and MultiCore versions included.</LI></UL> 
]]></ReleaseNotes>						

<Installation><![CDATA[
<B>Installing the Project Source Code</B>
<U>From the archive</U>
<UL><LI>Download the latest source code archive</LI>
<LI>Unzip the source code zip to any folder on your disk. For instance: </LI> 
c:\development\
<LI>You will see a AsyncCommand_X_Y (where X_Y is version) source folder. For instance: </LI></UL>  
c:\development\AsyncCommand_X_Y 

<U>From the Repository</U>
<UL><LI>Use your  favorite SVN client to retrieve the latest source code release from the repository.</LI></UL>     

<B>Using the Utility in Your Project</B>
<U>Add the Utility Library to your Project Using Flex Builder 3</U>
<UL><LI>Open or create a Flex or AIR Project in Flex Builder 3</LI>
<LI>From the Flex Builder menu, do:</LI>
Project -> Properties -> Flex Build Path -> Library Path -> Add SWC
<LI>Browse and select the SWC, for instance:</LI> 
c:\development\AsyncCommand_X_Y\bin\Utility_AS3_AsyncCommand_X_Y.swc
<LI>Click Finish.</LI></UL>  

<U>Add the Utility Library to your Flash/CS3/CS4 Project</U>
<UL><LI>The distributed SWC file will not work.</LI>
<LI>You must place the source code in your classpath.</LI>
<LI>Consult the CS3/CS4 documentation for the various ways to accomplish this.</LI></UL>  
]]></Installation>												

		</Project>
	</NodeMap>
</Node>