<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Node id="205907" name="XML Database" thumb="box">	
	<NodeMap>
		<Project 
			name="XML Database Utility for AS3" 
			status="Production"
			repo="Utility_AS3_AIR_XMLDatabase" 
			tag="XMLDatabase_1_2"
			version="1.2"
			archive="AS3/Utility_AS3_AIR_XMLDatabase.zip" 
			docs="AS3/Utility_AS3_AIR_XMLDatabase/asdoc/"
			live=""
			forum="topic=261"
			owner="Cliff Hall"
			owner_node="300"
			pic="PureMVC-Framework-AS3-Std-MC.png"
			shot="">
			
<Description><![CDATA[
This utility provides the ability for PureMVC-based AIR applications to easily create and persist and work with XML databases. 
]]></Description>						

<ReleaseNotes><![CDATA[
<B>Changes in 1.2</B>
<UL><LI>Added MultiCore support.</LI>
<LI>No Standard version functionality changes except renaming source tree, therefore, there is no need to migrate Standard version apps to 1.2 unless you're also migrating to MultiCore. </LI></UL>   

<B>Changes in 1.1</B>
<UL><LI>Moved source code into src folder. No functionality changed. </LI></UL>

<B>Features in 1.0</B>
<UL><LI>Abstract class for representing an XML database</LI>
<LI>Reads existing XML file or creates from a skeleton and persists</LI>
<LI>Handles File I/O automatically</LI>
<LI>Provides a way to parse the XML tree and delegate nodes to different proxies </LI>
<LI>Command for persisting arbitrary XML databases</LI>
<LI>Application can have as many XML databases as needed</LI></UL>

AIR applications can to store, retrieve and manipulate structured data. A great way to do this is with XML, since AS3 gives us powerful tools in E4X for manipulation of the data.
For now, see the CodePeek demo to understand how to implement in your app. 
]]></ReleaseNotes>						

<Installation><![CDATA[
<B>Installing the Project Source Code</B>
<U>From the archive</U>
<UL><LI>Download the latest source code archive</LI>
<LI>Unzip the source code zip to any folder on your disk. For instance: </LI> 
c:\development\
<LI>You will see a XMLDatabase_X_Y (where X_Y is version) source folder. For instance: </LI></UL>  
c:\development\XMLDatabase_X_Y 

<U>From the Repository</U>
<UL><LI>Use your favorite SVN client to retrieve the latest source code release from the repository.</LI></UL>     

<B>Using the Utility in Your Project</B>
<U>Add the Utility Library to your AIR Project Using Flex Builder 3</U>
<UL><LI>Open or create a AIR Project in Flex Builder 3</LI>
<LI>From the Flex Builder menu, do:</LI>
Project -> Properties -> Flex Build Path -> Library Path -> Add SWC
<LI>Browse and select the SWC, for instance:</LI> 
c:\development\XMLDatabase_X_Y\bin\Utility_AS3_AIR_XMLDatabase_X_Y.swc
<LI>Click Finish.</LI></UL>  

]]></Installation>												

		</Project>
	</NodeMap>
</Node>