<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Node id="502" name="German"  thumb="flag-germany">
	<NodeMap>
		<Nodes>
			<Node id="5020" name="Best Practices" thumb="box">
					<NodeMap>
						<Document 
							name="Best Practices and Implementation Idioms (German Translation)"
							author="Cliff Hall (Translated by Jens Krause)"
							doc_url="http://puremvc.org/component/option,com_wrapper/Itemid,182/"
							pic="PureMVC-IIBP-German.png"><![CDATA[
<P>And now for a big Danke schön to Jens Krause, who has recently completed the translation of the PureMVC Implementation Idioms and Best Practices document into German ( Implementierung Idiome und Optimale Anwendung ). As with the original, examples are in ActionScript 3 for Adobe Flex, Flash and AIR.</P>
<P>I have met Jens, and he speaks quite good conversational English. I have also seen him deliver a technical talk on PureMVC in his native German. From observing his delivery and subsequent Q and A session I gather that he is very adept at getting the details across to a German audience. This really makes him a great candidate for translation of the IIBP into German.</P>
<P>Further making him a shoe-in for the job, Jens is also a published author; his Analyse der Leistungssportförderung in der ehemaligen DDR: Am Beispiel ausgewählter Wintersportarten (Broschiert), delves into the pervasive "sport miracle GDR" myth, which is based on the considerable successes of former GDR (German Democratic Republic) athletes in various winter sports. How could a small Central European country like the GDR excel in world class winter sports although it could offer only modest conditions from a geographical and meteorological perspective?</P> 
<P>And finally, the number one quality gaining him the official German translator position - he actually volunteered to do it!  :)</P> 
<P>And thanks once again to Jens for this exacting effort,<BR/>
-=Cliff&gt;</P>
]]>						
							</Document>
					</NodeMap>
			</Node>
		</Nodes>
	</NodeMap>
</Node>