<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Node id="20542" name="AsyncStub" thumb="box">	
	<NodeMap>
		<Project 
			name="AsyncStub Utility for AS3" 
			status="Production"
			repo="Utility_AS3_AsyncStub" 
			tag="AsyncStub_1_2_5"
			version="1.2.5"
			archive="AS3/Utility_AS3_AsyncStub.zip" 
			docs="AS3/Utility_AS3_AsyncStub/asdoc/"
			live=""
			forum="topic=260.0"
			owner="Philip Sexton"
			owner_node="327"
			pic="PureMVC-Framework-AS3-Std-MC.png"
			shot="">
			
<Description><![CDATA[
The Asynchronous Stub utility consists of a Proxy which can be extended for the purpose of simulating asynchronous activity, by way of a random timer.
]]></Description>						

<ReleaseNotes><![CDATA[<B>Changes in Version 1.2.5</B>
  * No new features, but now includes multicore folder for multicore src 
  * The bin folder now includes the multicore swc.
  
<B>Changes in Version 1.2</B>
  * Refactored source into src folder.

<B>Changes in Version 1.1</B>
  * Enhanced to cater for fault outcome, with probability of fault.
  * Provide a token tracking feature.
  
<B>Features in Version 1.0</B>
  * Uses a timer to simulate asyncronous interaction with server
  * Simulates failure 

Occasionally, for testing a service before it is online, you may need a Proxy that acts as though it has asynchronously contacted a server and retrieved data. You may also need for it to simulate random load times, timeouts, and failures. This can be for testing purposes or as a stand-in until the actual service is in place so that client development can proceed.

The Flex-based demo called Loadup as Ordered provides an example use of this utility. 
]]></ReleaseNotes>						

<Installation><![CDATA[<B>Installing the Project Source Code</B>
<U>From the archive</U>
  * Download the latest source code archive.
  * Unzip the source code zip to any folder on your disk. 
	For instance: c:\development\
  * You will see a AsyncStub_X_Y (where X_Y is version) source folder. 
	For instance: c:\development\AsyncStub_X_Y 

<U>From the Repository</U>
  * Use your  favorite SVN client to retrieve the latest source code release from the repository.   

<B>Using the Utility in Your Project</B>
<I>Add the Utility Library to your Project Using Flex Builder 3</I>
  * Open or create a Flex or AIR Project in Flex Builder 3
  * From the Flex Builder menu, do: Project -> Properties -> Flex Build Path -> Library Path -> Add SWC
  * Browse and select the SWC (for instance: c:\development\AsyncStub\Utility_AS3_AsyncStub_X_Y.swc)
  * Click Finish. 

<I>Add the Utility Library to your Flash/CS3/CS4 Project</I>
  * The distributed SWC file will not work.
  * You must place the source code in your classpath.
  * Consult the CS3/CS4 documentation for the various ways to accomplish this.
]]></Installation>												

		</Project>
	</NodeMap>
</Node>