<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Node id="7" name="Presentations" thumb="section-presentations">
	<NodeMap>
		<Nodes>
		
			<!-- STANDARD VERSION OVERVIEW -->
			<Node id="700" name="Standard Overview" thumb="section-presentation">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="PureMVC Standard Version Overview" 
						site_url="http://puremvc.tv/#P100/"
						speaker="Cliff Hall"
						speaker_url="http://content.futurescale.com/component/option,com_contact/task,view/contact_id,1/Itemid,54/"
						pic="http://puremvc.tv/assets/art/standard/Title.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>A platform and language neutral introduction to the PureMVC Standard Version Framework delivered as a slideshow narrated by Cliff Hall on PureMVC TV.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- MULTICORE VERSION OVERVIEW -->
			<Node id="701" name="MultiCore Overview" thumb="section-presentation">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="PureMVC MultiCore Version Overview" 
						site_url="http://puremvc.tv/#P002/"
						speaker="Cliff Hall"
						speaker_url="http://content.futurescale.com/component/option,com_contact/task,view/contact_id,1/Itemid,54/"
						pic="http://puremvc.tv/assets/art/multicore/Title.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>A platform and language neutral introduction to the PureMVC MultiCore Version Framework delivered as a slideshow narrated by Cliff Hall on PureMVC TV.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- STATE MACHINE OVERVIEW -->
			<Node id="702" name="State Machine Overview" thumb="section-presentation">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="PureMVC State Machine Utility Overview" 
						site_url="http://puremvc.tv/#P003/"
						speaker="Cliff Hall"
						speaker_url="http://content.futurescale.com/component/option,com_contact/task,view/contact_id,1/Itemid,54/"
						pic="http://puremvc.tv/assets/art/statemachine/Title.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>A platform and language neutral introduction to the PureMVC State Machine Utility delivered as a slideshow narrated by Cliff Hall on PureMVC TV.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- GETTING IN THE GROOVE -->
			<Node id="703" name="Getting in the Groove" thumb="section-presentation">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="Getting in the Groove" 
						site_url="http://puremvc.tv/#P004/"
						speaker="Cliff Hall"
						speaker_url="http://content.futurescale.com/component/option,com_contact/task,view/contact_id,1/Itemid,54/"
						pic="http://puremvc.tv/assets/art/groove/Title.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>Just a short time ago, I upgraded my old <a href="http://seaofarrows.com" target="_blank"/>Sea of Arrows</A> music site to a Flex-based PureMVC MultiCore application.</P>
<P>I had grown a bit tired of the old site which was a terrible HTML/Flash thing that had been thrown together in haste. Talk about the shoemaker's kids running around barefoot. So I reasoned that the overhaul could stand as a non-trivial PureMVC / Multicore / Pipes / StateMachine demo and went for it.</P>
<P>Once it was up, somehow the idea struck me that I could reuse this mp3 player/visualizer codebase to show presentations in a unique way. Playlists and Tracks would become Presentations and narrated Slides.</P>
<P>Rather than record a single half hour audio or video presentation, I could instead create the audio for each slide separately, and since the app supports deeplinking, I could perhaps use them as "Talking FAQ's," linking directly to apropos slides in forum posts and such.</P>
<P>The result is now up and running. At PureMVC TV you'll currently find 4 short overview presentations on PureMVC, MultiCore, StateMachine, and finally Getting in the Groove, which documents the approach used to power both Sea of Arrows and PureMVC TV.</P>
<P>The common code has been extracted into a new library called MediaTurbine, which both sites are now running. The business of creating a site like either of these has now been reduced to extending a single class, defining the CSS and XML configuration and supplying its media assets.</P>
<P>There are a few rough edges, sure. But just try to argue that you can't get immediate and gratifying code reuse with OOP, I dare you! :) </P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- FRAMEWORK SHOOTOUT -->
			<Node id="704" name="Framework Shootout" thumb="section-presentation">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="Framework Shootout at the SilvaFUG Corral" 
						site_url="https://admin.adobe.acrobat.com/_a200985228/p12266504/"
						speaker="Luke Bayes and Ali Mills"
						speaker_url="http://www.asserttrue.com/articles/2007/10/17/silvafug-application-frameworks-presentation"
						pic="PureMVC-Preso-SilvaFUG.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>Luke Bayes and Ali Mills of PatternPark really did their homework as they prepared their presentation for the Silicon Valley Flex Users Group (SilvaFUG), held at Adobe's offices in San Francisco.</P>
<P>They gave their assessments of 9 different frameworks and toolkits for creating Flex applications. Reviewed and ranked were Cairngorm, PureMVC, ARP, MVCS, Flest, Model-Glue: Flex, ServerBox Foundry, Guasax, and Slide.  They shared their experiences with each, and ranked them based on Approachability, Flexibility and Scalability.</P>
<P>In order to evaluate the frameworks on an equal basis, they designed a simple task list application, and attempted to build it using each of the frameworks.</P>
<P>And the final verdict? Of all 9 frameworks considered, PureMVC was ranked most approachable, flexible and scalable.</P>
<P>Luke Bayes writes in his follow up: </P>
<P><U>"If you don’t have the patience to watch the whole thing online our conclusion was that PureMVC by Cliff Hall beats out the alternatives. We prefer PureMVC because of: Composition over inheritence, liberal use of interfaces, indirection is used but not overwhelming, instance members hide singleton references from application code, and MXML views can be extremely thin. All the benefits of Cairngorm, with few of the disadvantages.
    </U></P><P>After delivering the findings of their investigation, the audience became very involved. A lot of good and practical questions were raised and a healthy discussion ensued. Source code for their TooDoo application written in both Cairngorm and PureMVC are available on their blog, as well as the slideshow and a streaming video recording of the presentation.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>
			
			<!-- ATL USER GROUP -->
			<Node id="705" name="Atlanta Meetup" thumb="section-presentation">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="PureMVC @ Atlanta Meetup 12/18/2008" 
						site_url="http://adobechats.adobe.acrobat.com/p88582617/"
						speaker="Cliff Hall"
						speaker_url="http://content.futurescale.com/component/option,com_contact/task,view/contact_id,1/Itemid,54/"
						pic="PureMVC-Preso-AAFUG.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>Cliff Hall recently delivered an introductory talk on the PureMVC framework to the Adobe Flex User Group in Atlanta. The recording is available online.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- SAN DIEGO USER GROUP -->
			<Node id="706" name="San Diego Meetup" thumb="section-presentation">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="PureMVC @ San Diego Meetup 1/21/2009" 
						site_url="http://experts.na3.acrobat.com/p41582221/"
						speaker="Cliff Hall"
						speaker_url="http://content.futurescale.com/component/option,com_contact/task,view/contact_id,1/Itemid,54/"
						pic="PureMVC-Preso-SDAUG.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>Cliff Hall delivered an introductory talk on the PureMVC framework to the Adobe User Group in San Diego via Acrobat Connect. The recording is available online.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- HELLO WORLD GROUP -->
			<Node id="707" name="'Hello World' Introduction" thumb="section-presentation">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="Adobe TV: 'Hello World' Intro to PureMVC" 
						site_url="http://tv.adobe.com/watch/adc-presents/intro-to-puremvc/"
						speaker="Cornel Creanga"
						speaker_url="http://cornelcreanga.com/"
						pic="PureMVC-Preso-ADC-Intro.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>Cornel Creanga has posted a short video introduction to PureMVC with a Flex-based 'Hello World' application sample. It focuses on the key actors involved in sending a message to the server, and then displaying the response.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- PIRATE HQ -->
			<Node id="707" name="Pirate HQ @ MAX '08" thumb="section-presentation">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="Pirate Internet Radio Conference Takeover @ MAX '08" 
						site_url="http://connectpro78922856.acrobat.com/p13537877"
						speaker="Cap'n Cliff Hall and his Scurvy Crew"
						speaker_url="http://content.futurescale.com/component/option,com_contact/task,view/contact_id,1/Itemid,54/"
						pic="PureMVC-Preso-PirateHQ.png"><![CDATA[Speakers as they appear in the recording:
    <U>0:00:00 - Cliff Hall - Welcome</U>
    <font color="#0000FF"><a href="http://puremvc.org" target="_blank">http://puremvc.org</A></font>
    PureMVC Project Architect and Head Pirate Cliff Hall introduces the lineup and otherwise puts in a full pirate's day trying to keep the ship on an even keel. Just stayin' afloat with the extreme packet loss we suffered at the HQ was a chore. We had to fireman's carry the bit buckets back and forth constantly just to keep from going under! Despite it all, she was a yar rig and we managed to come out nearly unscathed! ARRH!

    <U>0:00:50 - Brendan Lee - BT/Ribbit - Ribbit API </U>
    <font color="#0000FF"><a href="http://ribbit.com" target="_blank">http://ribbit.com</A></font>
    Ribbit has created a telephony platform based on PureMVC which allows you to easily add VOIP and SMS to your Flex, Flash and AIR pplications. Speaking about the Ribbit platform and some of the exciting things going on there is one of the key developers on the project, Brendan Lee.

    <U>0:16:00 - Dominic Gelineau - Twist Image - Think in Colour and Redefining Floors </U> 
	<font color="#0000FF"><a href="http://www.homedepot.ca/thinkincolour" target="_blank">http://www.homedepot.ca/thinkincolour</A> <a href="http://www.homedepot.ca/redefiningfloors" target="_blank">http://www.homedepot.ca/redefiningfloors</A></font>
    HomeDepot has launched two similar Flash applications called "Think in colour" and "Redefining floors" which to help the customer choose Paint and Flooring. One of those applications was built on PureMVC and one wasn't. Dominic Gélineau is a Flash rogrammer at Twist Image who worked on both projects, and he describes the differences between the two apps from development perspective.

    <U>0:30:00 - Daniel Swid - Latenite Labs - Reactor and Radience</U>
    <font color="#0000FF"><a href="http://latenitelabs.com" target="_blank">http://latenitelabs.com</A></font>
    Late Nite Labs provides a virtual lab solution for distance learning education. The problem with distance learning science courses, such as biology and chemistry is the lab requirement. Late Nite's Reactor and Radience apps, are able to fulfill the academic requirement and schools can save on lab expenses. Speaking about Reactor and Radience is Daniel Swid, a developer on the project at Late Nite Labs.

    <U>0:43:00 - Javier Julio - Arc90 - Kindling</U>
    <font color="#0000FF"><a href="http://kindlingapp.com/" target="_blank">http://kindlingapp.com/</A></font>
    If you've ever tried to promote an idea within a large company and had difficulty getting any joy, you'll appreciate Kindling. Javier Julio works for Arc90, a midtown Manhattan web consulting and product firm. He introduces Kindling, Arc90's first product which is a web-based idea management application and be demoing a standalone AIR client he developed using
    Kindling's REST API.
     
    <U>1:13:00 - Clause Wahlers - côdeazur brasil - Aupeo</U>
    <font color="#0000FF"><a href="http://aupeo.com/" target="_blank">http://aupeo.com/</A></font>
    Claus Wahlers, a became a personal icon of mine when he co-authored FC64 - a Flash based Commodore 64 emulator that actually runs all the ld games that many of us knew and loved. Sadly the FC64 wasn't built on PureMVC, but Claus's latest project is. AUPEO! is a new music driven social networking platform. And here today to talk with us about it is none other than Claus himself.

    <U>1:34:00 - Bobby Parker - Blue Bear, LLC - Kodiak</U>
    <font color="#0000FF"><a href="http://bluebearllc.net/kodiak/" target="_blank">http://bluebearllc.net/kodiak/</A></font>
	Kodiak, from BlueBear, enables unprecedented visibility into and control over virtualized infrastructures, regardless of size or composition. As the industry's only application that's both hypervisor-agnostic and cross-platform, Kodiak sets a new standard in versatility, pushing virtualization out of the datacenter and catalyzing its widespread adoption throughout the information technology landscape. BlueBear believes useful software should be available to anybody who needs it, and at no cost; hence Kodiak's price, totally free! 

    2:11:00 - Nick Collins - Sogeti, USA - PureMVC Studio
    Code generation has been a subject of much discussion in the PureMVC community since its inception, and several products out there already support it to some extent. Nick Collins is the author of PureMVC Studio which allows you to quickly and visually lay out your application skeleton, complete with multiple cores, views, proxies, value objects, notifications, commands, and additionally custom singletons or generic classes. Each of these classes are then generated from user customizable templates and a fully importable Eclipse/FlexBuilder project is generated. The application allows you to target either the browser, or AIR platform, as well as choose whether you want your view code to be MXML based or pure AS3.
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			
		</Nodes>
	</NodeMap>
</Node>