<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Node id="7" name="Presentations" thumb="flake">
	<NodeMap>
		<Nodes>
		
			<!-- STANDARD VERSION OVERVIEW -->
			<Node id="700" name="Standard Overview" thumb="box">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="PureMVC Standard Version Overview" 
						site_url="http://puremvc.tv/#P100/"
						author="Cliff Hall"
						author_url="http://futurescale.com"
						pic="http://puremvc.tv/assets/icon/standard/title.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>A platform and language neutral introduction to the PureMVC Standard Version Framework delivered as a slideshow narrated by Cliff Hall on PureMVC TV.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- MULTICORE VERSION OVERVIEW -->
			<Node id="701" name="MultiCore Overview" thumb="box">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="PureMVC MultiCore Version Overview" 
						site_url="http://puremvc.tv/#P002/"
						author="Cliff Hall"
						author_url="http://futurescale.com"
						pic="http://puremvc.tv/assets/icon/multicore/title.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>A platform and language neutral introduction to the PureMVC MultiCore Version Framework delivered as a slideshow narrated by Cliff Hall on PureMVC TV.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- STATE MACHINE OVERVIEW -->
			<Node id="702" name="State Machine Overview" thumb="box">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="PureMVC State Machine Utility Overview" 
						site_url="http://puremvc.tv/#P003/"
						author="Cliff Hall"
						author_url="http://futurescale.com"
						pic="http://puremvc.tv/assets/icon/statemachine/title.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>A platform and language neutral introduction to the PureMVC State Machine Utility delivered as a slideshow narrated by Cliff Hall on PureMVC TV.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- GETTING IN THE GROOVE -->
			<Node id="703" name="Getting in the Groove" thumb="box">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="Getting in the Groove: The Creation of Media Turbine." 
						site_url="http://puremvc.tv/#P004/"
						author="Cliff Hall"
						author_url="http://futurescale.com"
						pic="http://puremvc.tv/assets/icon/groove/title.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>Just a short time ago, I upgraded my old <a href="http://seaofarrows.com" target="_blank"/>Sea of Arrows</A> music site to a Flex-based PureMVC MultiCore application.</P>
<P>I had grown a bit tired of the old site which was a terrible HTML/Flash thing that had been thrown together in haste. Talk about the shoemaker's kids running around barefoot. So I reasoned that the overhaul could stand as a non-trivial PureMVC / Multicore / Pipes / StateMachine demo and went for it.</P>
<P>Once it was up, somehow the idea struck me that I could reuse this mp3 player/visualizer codebase to show presentations in a unique way. Playlists and Tracks would become Presentations and narrated Slides.</P>
<P>Rather than record a single half hour audio or video presentation, I could instead create the audio for each slide separately, and since the app supports deeplinking, I could perhaps use them as "Talking FAQ's," linking directly to apropos slides in forum posts and such.</P>
<P>The result is now up and running. At PureMVC TV you'll currently find 4 short overview presentations on PureMVC, MultiCore, StateMachine, and finally Getting in the Groove, which documents the approach used to power both Sea of Arrows and PureMVC TV.</P>
<P>The common code has been extracted into a new library called MediaTurbine, which both sites are now running. The business of creating a site like either of these has now been reduced to extending a single class, defining the CSS and XML configuration and supplying its media assets.</P>
<P>There are a few rough edges, sure. But just try to argue that you can't get immediate and gratifying code reuse with OOP, I dare you! :) </P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- FRAMEWORK SHOOTOUT -->
			<Node id="704" name="Framework Shootout" thumb="box">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="Framework Shootout at the SilvaFUG Corral" 
						site_url="https://admin.adobe.acrobat.com/_a200985228/p12266504/"
						author="Luke Bayes and Ali Mills"
						author_url="http://www.asserttrue.com/articles/2007/10/17/silvafug-application-frameworks-presentation"
						pic="http://puremvc.org/images/stories/SilvaFUGFrameworksPreso.jpg">
<![CDATA[
<P>Image Luke Bayes and Ali Mills of PatternPark really did their homework as they prepared for their recent presentation for the Silicon Valley Flex Users Group (SilvaFUG), held at Adobe's offices in San Francisco.</P>
<P>They gave their assessments of 9 different frameworks and toolkits for creating Flex applications. Reviewed and ranked were Cairngorm, PureMVC, ARP, MVCS, Flest, Model-Glue: Flex, ServerBox Foundry, Guasax, and Slide.  They shared their experiences with each, and ranked them based on Approachability, Flexibility and Scalability.</P>
<P>In order to evaluate the frameworks on an equal basis, they designed a simple task list application, and attempted to build it using each of the frameworks.</P>
<P>And the final verdict? Of all 9 frameworks considered, PureMVC was ranked most approachable, flexible and scalable.</P>
<P>Luke Bayes writes in his follow up: </P>
<P><I>
    "If you don’t have the patience to watch the whole thing online our conclusion was that PureMVC by Cliff Hall beats out the alternatives.<BR/>
    We prefer PureMVC because of:<BR/>
    <UL>
    <LI>Composition over inheritence</LI>
    <LI>Liberal use of Interfaces</LI>
    <LI>Indirection is used but not overwhelming</LI>
    <LI>Instance members hide singleton references from application code</LI>
    <LI>MXML views can be extremely thin</LI>
    <LI>Benefits of Cairngorm, with few of the disadvantages.</LI>
    </UL></I></P>
    <P>After delivering the findings of their investigation, the audience became very involved. A lot of good and practical questions were raised and a healthy discussion ensued. Source code for their TooDoo application written in both Cairngorm and PureMVC are available on their blog, as well as the slideshow and a streaming video recording of the presentation.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>
			
			<!-- ATL USER GROUP -->
			<Node id="705" name="Atlanta Meetup" thumb="box">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="Adobe Flex User Group Atlanta: PureMVC Framework 12/18/2008" 
						site_url="http://adobechats.adobe.acrobat.com/p88582617/"
						author="Cliff Hall"
						author_url="http://futurescale.com"
						pic="http://puremvc.tv/assets/icon/standard/title.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>Cliff Hall recently delivered an introductory talk on the PureMVC framework to the Adobe Flex User Group in Atlanta. The recording is available online.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- SAN DIEGO USER GROUP -->
			<Node id="706" name="San Diego Meetup" thumb="box">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="Adobe User Group San Diego: PureMVC Framework 1/21/2009" 
						site_url="http://experts.na3.acrobat.com/p41582221/"
						author="Cliff Hall"
						author_url="http://futurescale.com"
						pic="http://puremvc.tv/assets/icon/standard/title.png">
<![CDATA[
<P>Cliff Hall recently delivered an introductory talk on the PureMVC framework to the Adobe User Group in San Diego. The recording is available online.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			<!-- HELLO WORLD GROUP -->
			<Node id="707" name="'Hello World' Introduction" thumb="box">
				<NodeMap>
					<Presentation 
						name="Adobe TV: 'Hello World' Intro to PureMVC" 
						site_url="http://tv.adobe.com/watch/adc-presents/intro-to-puremvc/"
						author="Cornel Creanga"
						author_url="http://cornelcreanga.com/"
						pic="http://thumbnails.tv.adobe.com/adc-presents100.jpg">
<![CDATA[
<P>Cornel Creanga has posted a short video introduction to PureMVC with a Flex-based 'Hello World' application sample. It focuses on the key actors involved in sending a message to the server, and then displaying the response.</P>
]]>						
						</Presentation>
				</NodeMap>
			</Node>

			
		</Nodes>
	</NodeMap>
</Node>