<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Node id="205408" name="Desktop Citizen" thumb="box">	
	<NodeMap>
		<Project 
			name="Desktop Citizen Utility for AS3" 
			status="Production"
			repo="Utility_AS3_AIR_DesktopCitizen" 
			tag="DesktopCitizen_1_2_1"
			version="1.2.1"
			archive="AS3/Utility_AS3_AIR_DesktopCitizen.zip" 
			docs="AS3/Utility_AS3_AIR_DesktopCitizen/asdoc/"
			srcview="AS3/Utility_AS3_AIR_DesktopCitizen/srcview/"
			live=""
			forum="topic=262"
			owner="Cliff Hall"
			owner_node="300"
			pic="PureMVC-Framework-AS3-Std-MC.png"
			shot="">
			
<Description><![CDATA[
This utility provides the ability for PureMVC-based AIR applications remember their window size, position and maximized state each time it is launched.
]]></Description>						

<ReleaseNotes><![CDATA[
<B>Changes in 1.2.1</B>
<UL><LI>Moved constructor actions to onRegister.</LI></UL> 

<B>Changes in 1.2</B>
<UL><LI>Added MultiCore support.</LI>
<LI>No Standard version functionality changes except renaming source tree, therefore, there is no need to migrate Standard version apps to 1.2 unless you're also migrating to MultiCore. </LI></UL> 

<B>Changes in 1.1</B>
<UL><LI>Moved source code into src folder. No functionality changed. </LI></UL>

<B>Features in 1.0</B>
<UL><LI>Manages an XML Database with the information about the main application window's position, size and state (WindowMetrics)</LI>
<LI>Reads the Window Metrics at startup, applies to the main window then sends a notification that the window is ready to be shown.</LI>
<LI>Allows the window to be sized and positioned BEFORE being shown so that it doesn't flash up at a default size, then resize, causing visual repaint.  </LI>
<LI>See the demos CodePeek and RSSHeadlines for example use of this utility. </LI></UL>
]]></ReleaseNotes>						

<Installation><![CDATA[
<B>Installing the Project Source Code</B>
<U>From the archive</U>
<UL><LI>Download the latest source code archive</LI>
<LI>Unzip the source code zip to any folder on your disk. For instance: </LI> 
c:\development\
<LI>You will see a DesktopCitizen_X_Y (where X_Y is version) source folder. For instance: </LI></UL>  
c:\development\DesktopCitizen_X_Y 

<U>From the Repository</U>
<UL><LI>Use your favorite SVN client to retrieve the latest source code release from the repository.</LI></UL>     

<B>Using the Utility in Your Project</B>
<U>Add the Utility Library to your AIR Project Using Flex Builder 3</U>
<UL><LI>Open or create a AIR Project in Flex Builder 3</LI>
<LI>From the Flex Builder menu, do:</LI>
Project -> Properties -> Flex Build Path -> Library Path -> Add SWC
<LI>Browse and select the SWC, for instance:</LI> 
c:\development\DesktopCitizen_X_Y\bin\Utility_AS3_AIR_DesktopCitizen_X_Y.swc
<LI>Click Finish.</LI></UL>  

		</Project>
	</NodeMap>
</Node>